HAN JEONG-U, TRAUMA CLEANER
SANG-GU'S OLDER BROTHER!
MAKE SURE THEY MEET!
ONE MESSAGE FROM UNCLE CHO SANG-GU
DON'T WAIT FOR ME
I'M NOT COMING BACK
PORORO BAND-AID FOR KIDS
LOOKING FOR MY MISSING UNCLE
LAST SEEN ON JUNE 7TH
FILTHY, LOUD, GOOD AT FIGHTING
CONTACT IF YOU'VE SEEN HIM
MISSED CALLS: GEU-RU, NA-MU, MADAM
MADAM: YOUR NEPHEW IS LOOKING FOR YOU
LOOKING FOR MY MISSING UNCLE
PLEDGE
NAME: CHO SANG-GU
MOVE TO HEAVEN
CHICKEN
CHINESE RESTAURANT
YEAR 1994
DO NOT CROSS THE DANGEROUS TRACKS
CONDOLENCES
ONE YEAR LATER
SUIN STATION
SAFETY FIRST, DO NOT ENTER
4, HANEULSAN-RO 29-GIL
LOOKING FOR MY MISSING BROTHER
NAME: CHO SANG-GU
AGE: 10, BORN IN 1986
LAST SEE ON JUNE 30TH, 1995
SAMPOONG DEPARTMENT STORE
SANG-GU, HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!
HAPPY 14TH BIRTHDAY, SANG-GU
JUNE 29TH, 1999 FROM JEONG-U
HAPPY 15TH BIRTHDAY, SANG-GU
JUNE 29TH, 2000 FROM JEONG-U
CERTIFICATION OF ADOPTION
NAME: HAN GEU-RU
Subtitle translation by: Jean S Kim